{
    "id": "e5421b3262544974aa7708a90ffe4b3f",
    "title": "Many and many of | grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7fe66202f5f2472ab4519be2ceef5c0c",
            "title": "Many And Many Of",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "……………… families own cars these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. us were disappointed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. them were late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Many",
                        "Many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There were ……………….. children among the audience.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How …………………. you can solve this?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have thought about him …………………. times.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Yes, ……………….. us are interested in the proposal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There were ……………… people who didn’t like the idea.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have told you this ………………. times.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have seen her ……………….. times.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "many of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}